in 60 days I'm gonna turn these hundred
dollars into a million dollars
everything is going to be documented on
my YouTube Instagram telegram so you
guys follow along on this challenge that
I'm taking that nobody's ever done and
I'm currently on my second attempt and
the first attempt was last week where I
was in London where I was trading London
session in real time and guess what
happened to the challenge I blew it but
I learned two very valuable lessons in
last week's Challenge and that is to not
set and forget too much and not be
greedy those lessons I'm applying to
this challenge in this week so we can
take this journey taking a hundred
dollar to a million dollar challenge
let's hope we don't blow this next
account and we hopefully don't get a
third of so let's get started
all right so this is week two of The
Challenge and my second account and
we're finally back home in my Miami
office where this challenge just got a
whole lot serious because we're back
home so we're gonna take this just
serious I'm gonna be showing you guys
the trays that I am going to be trading
this week the trade that I already
currently got in which I got three
phones to show you guys like the same
trade on all of the phones and then what
trades I'm gonna be looking for it to
take on this week because you guys saw
how fast I go last week and if I keep
that same strategy it don't get too
greedy and I learned from my lessons
from last week we can pass this
challenge probably not under 60 days
probably a little bit more but we're
gonna make the attempt so put the three
phones to the side so you guys see all
the same trades now let's break down the
trades that I'm gonna be taking this
week so right now as you can tell we are
in AUD Cod AUD Cod same exact trade on
all the phones so AUD CAD is bearish on
the higher time frames such as the daily
and the weekly and in the daily time
frame we've come to retest structure
structure and structure level so this is
clearly a strong area of Interest
whenever we are under reselling whenever
we're under selling whenever we're above
we're buying and in this case we are
under so this is where I go down to the
lower time frame such as the one hour 30
minute 50 minute and this is where I
look for my entry signal and as you guys
can tell here we had a shift of
structure shift the structure is when
the market does this it is bullish and
the moment we shift meaning we break
under the structure point this is where
I enter the trade short which is exactly
the same exact thing that happened here
we shifted structure but we were not at
the area of Interest the area of
interest is this alarm appears this zone
so this exact same shift the structure
happens at the area of engine that's why
it is so key to learn how to put these
air Adventures so took this trade I'm
gonna even show you guys how I called it
in the telegrams look look over here in
the telegram you guys can see the
telegram I sent this today July 31st
look at the date and the time up there
so July 31st trade looks solid looking
for any sales right now and that was at
9 30 so that was about an hour hour ago
did you see the time up there and then
this is the result of that trade as of
right now so this is the first trade for
the week and the second trade for the
week is going to be Euro GBP so we come
here to Euro GBP kind of the same thing
we're at a very strong daily area of
Interest we have support support support
resistance support so whenever we're
above it we're clearly heading to the
upside and as of right now right here we
are above it so this is where I go down
to the four hour and I see the
accumulation happening at this area so
this is where I go down to the same
thing the lower time frame since the one
hour 30 minute 15 minute and I literally
Drew this line right here and I expected
for price to have a retest to then head
to the upside and I'm going to even show
you guys how I caught this with my
students on my Sunday call and I do
every single week with them so this is
the recording from the video is the
recording that I did last week and as
you guys can tell here these are the
trades that I was breaking down and this
same exact trade is AUD CAD if you zoom
in all the way up here you see AUD cat
which is the retest of the structure
structure structure that's exactly what
happened and then the trade after that
one is going to be the Euro GBP which is
the pullback to the area of Interest
pull back to the air of Interest then
head to the upside so this week we have
an interesting week we are as of right
now already up a total of about 30
dollars just so you know it's a stock
all right so trade update trade update
right now so here we have AUD CAD so
we're up probably earlier I think it was
like 20 I believe so it is currently 8
P.M of Miami time and this is us right
now in trading view as you guys can tell
we are waiting for the break of the
neckline of The Head and Shoulders we
have left head right shoulder so if we
close under this line I'm going to be
waiting for a retest to them sell that
is to take our next entry and then if
not if this trade breaks above that
means it hits our stop loss if you
notice I have an alarm at our stop loss
and I have an alarm here to enter our
next trade and then on top of that we
have your GBP which in order for me to
take this trade I was looking to enter
here earlier I would need this movement
to happen but for now I'm only going to
focus on the trade we are currently in
which is AUD Cod which is going to be
the break of that structure level and
this is how the trade is looking right
now so in the meantime we're gonna take
this baby to go drift finally got the
quick release on it so let's see how it
goes
[Music]
this is how we're looking right now
after a little bit of a drift session so
we're rejecting the area basically where
we enter the ready I'm still waiting for
the close of that to enter the trade so
this is how your account is right now so
we're up about 23 right now
um yeah let's go ahead a little bit more
drift and we keep setting forget
thank you
there it goes oh you do that often huh
running the gas like midriff
so trade update so this is currently
right now how we're looking so exactly
how I explain we're looking for the
break of the neckline and the retest so
you guys can see we're having that as we
speak right now I'm gonna give it about
another 15 20 minutes for us for me to
get my entry signal at this area uh
because we've been waiting this whole
entire time for my friends to put up
with the gas so the trade right now is
up 30 so I'm gonna enter a new trade uh
very soon but instead of forgetting we
ran out of gas so we can keep drifting
because it's currently 11 o'clock at
night Monday night so we got plenty of
time
[Music]
all right so just got home right now an
hour and a half later what a mission so
we don't know what's wrong with it we
barely made it home you guys saw the
clip and we have some water in here oil
or whatever I'm not a mechanic I'm just
a driver I can just whip the out of
it but I don't even know what engine
this is so um now we gotta call the
mechanic time to come tomorrow and tune
it but we'll check in tomorrow in the
morning to see how the trades are going
it's cool like I said once
trade update right now on AUD Cod
exactly what I explained about an hour
ago I ended up just I ended up taking it
but I didn't look at it and so then my
Discord is literally blowing up from all
of the students Pete the trade exactly
what I mentioned we're gonna get a
retest of this area to enter the trade
short this is where I entered the trade
and then I put my stop loss in the exact
same point where my previous trade is
had a quick Spike and then look at this
where it is now again seven forget for
the win once again so we're up about
right now and 90 on this trade I'm gonna
definitely keep on holding this trade
but I'm gonna keep in mind that we could
have a pullback probably during London
session so let's say we have a pullback
something like this so then we then head
to the downside once again so I'm gonna
learn my lesson from last week and not
get greedy that is the key to this
challenge because of right now exactly
what I explained in trade is exactly
what happened we took the first entry we
got multiple entries stop loss so it's
perfectly placed and then I explain once
we break we enter the retest so then we
sell stop losses in the original place
look at that bro so I'll update you guys
tomorrow in the morning all right guys
so it's the next morning of this trade
that we took last night don't have the
filming here so I kind of have to do it
on my phone so I'm gonna flip the phone
now and I'm gonna show you guys exactly
what I said was going to happen happened
once again and how and where the account
is right now so as you guys can see this
is an update on how the trades are going
this is live update as you guys can tell
everything here is live we're gonna put
what time is it in Miami and I'm gonna
refresh the page it is 7 58 and you guys
see here that I am refreshing it you go
to the top right of my screen and it is
7 58 so if you look at the trade it is
exactly what I explained I am explaining
how I was gonna enter up here and then
how I was gonna enter the retest of this
and I will simply
forget like I am literally calling every
single trade so I was up throughout
London and I was just watching this
continuing into the downside now I'm
gonna debate whether I should close
where we are and call it a trade because
this is exactly where I was last week
and I ended up holding too much and I
ended up blowing the account so I could
stay up about
458 on the account then I can then flip
this to about a thousand five hundred on
my next couple of Trades but this is
looking very solid right now we might be
having a pool tour around this area
right here they pull back to here to
then head straight down to this side but
I have to ask myself so is it worth it
for it to pull back maybe even higher to
then go down or should I just lock in
the profits where I'm in right now so
I'm gonna literally debate that in the
next 15 minutes because I kind of like
how this 30 minute count is to close
because if we do manage to close under
this line right here like if we man
managed to body clothes under this then
this is just going to continue taking
this tray to the downside like this so I
just it's just just a matter of time I
just gotta wait um but as far as the
other trays that I was looking to take
for example GBP CAD uh remember how I
drew out this little box yesterday and I
explained I'm like okay as soon as we
break out of the box I'm going to be
looking to take the tray long well would
you look at that it happened once again
this is the trade that we took on Friday
of last week which was this trade that I
then pulled out before it pulled back
and now we're back at the same area so
I'm just gonna do the same exact thing
that I did here so that is the trade
that gave us the 100 using profit and I
explained it again and it happened once
again I just didn't take it because I
was focused on the other trade all right
so this is trade up there right here so
you guys can see we have three phones
again four seven no 4512 and these are
the two trades that we just caught on
the trade so everything is live so I'm
gonna show you guys what happened after
I closed the trade which is exactly what
I wanted to happen and what I'm expected
to happen for the remaining of this week
because if it goes like this I can flip
it to probably a thousand a thousand two
hundred fifty by the end of this week so
let's check it so as you guys can tell I
closed the trade right around this area
right here because I was explaining how
we can have a bigger pool back to the
other side so then sell but we kept
shifting to the downside we retested
this area exactly how I mentioned I
mentioned if we body close under this
line right here we'll keep heading to
the downside and that's the case I don't
jump into a trade right now because
we're no longer in session so I'm just
gonna simply wait until to London
session tonight to take another trade
but I do expect this trade to have
potentially a little pullback into
around this area before actually then
continuing to the downside so this is
where I'm going to be looking for new
cells on this trade
um I ideally if I were to be trading a
normal account I would still be holding
these two trades but obviously for the
challenge purposes I closed earlier not
getting greedy all right so Market
updates so let me show you guys right
now I'm going to show you guys my
excellent but before that I want to make
sure so I show you guys that it is
Tuesday 9 34 Miami time I'm literally
like refreshing the website you guys can
see up here at the top right corner that
it is hold on one second that it is
August 934 so I'm going to show you guys
here on the three phones your account by
lessons and then I'm gonna show you guys
the my effects book doesn't get any more
legit than this so let me show you as
you can tell here phone one 472 these
are the trades that got us to that and
then this is just like the third phone
to verify right so now I'm going to be
showing you guys the myfx book which I
can officially show you because uh I've
officially closed the position so let me
show you three trees that we've taken
right here we've taken the AUD card
we've take two trades which are these
exact two trades right here which these
were the last two trades we took so you
can see it right here auv had two trades
and then we took one trade on gvp Cad
and that's what gave us uh these profits
right here so as of right now I know
obviously it is a lot but realistically
it's not much right because we just
flipped it from 100 to uh 450 one so let
me show you what I'm expecting to happen
for the next session so as you guys can
tell this is an update on the trade that
I took earlier this morning and we ended
up closing around this level over here
we ended up closing around this level
here remember we had the head and
shoulders we had the retest and the big
push I closed around here in the morning
and now what I am expecting for this
price to do is still the same thing as I
explained earlier and that's have a
retracement into this area so then it
has the continuation cells to the
downside so I'm expecting for this price
now to have a pullback into here and if
my entry signal aligns at this area in
here around this level of support to be
used as resistance then I enter and then
the next trade that I'm interested in is
Euro GBP eurogbp I'm going to be waiting
for a little pullback into this area
right here if you notice I'm just
waiting for this pullback we already
predicted the push now I'm waiting for
the pullback to then have the next push
I have my alarm arm set here and I have
my alarm set here so that's basically
going to let me know when price gets to
those areas that's when I apply the
center figure strategy to see if we
enter so with that being said I will be
seeing you guys tomorrow on the next
market update see you guys tomorrow so I
mean kind of reflecting now hey five
years ago I would do anything to own one
of these cards or to just even be inside
of the car and this is probably like my
seven eighth Supercar and I don't even
get surprised anymore like obviously
like it's fun to drive it puts a smile
on my face but there's nothing exciting
about it like I used to do anything to
be in one of these cars and now that I
own them it's not a big deal like I get
inside of it I don't even realize I'm in
a Supercar like I'm in a red light I'm
like bro why are these people picking at
me I'm
quarter million
America and it just kind of shows you
the potential that this trading industry
can give you because really
realistically money's just numbers on
the screen turn it from numbers on the
screen into a car like this where you
can have and after you have fun with it
so long it just turns into your normal
one it's kind of crazy how training has
gotten me to this because like if you
would have met me five years ago I would
have been at Dunkin Donuts and now I'm
in a McLaren that it's just another car
to me honestly but another another car
can't do this to make sure no cops so
I'm gonna do a 40 roll second the
attraction
oh
all right guys so it is Wednesday
morning as you guys can see right here
this is literally the open of New York
session let's just see what happened
last night so bear with me I'm holding
the camera set us isn't here to film it
so I got the camera and I'm doing it
through the phone I'm gonna be showing
you guys exactly what I said was going
to happen happen and on top of that the
trade that we got in this challenge is
getting a lot a lot more real so let me
flip the camera and get you guys there
so as you guys can see I'm here on the
website which it says what time is it in
Miami August 2nd 8 59 in the morning I'm
like refreshing it every single time now
we're gonna head over to trading View
and you guys can see here in trading
view before I actually show you the
trade that we are in let me show you
guys AUD cat this is the trade that I
was explaining yesterday I was literally
explaining to you guys how I was looking
for price to pull back to this area
right here in order for me to take the
trade to the downside and that is
exactly what we did like I'm talking
about to the T but the only issue is
that my alarm never activated so never
took a trade but literally happened
exactly how I explained I wanted the
price to come back into this area in
order to sell this is where we closed
the trade yesterday and I stuck to my
plan on not being greedy and not holding
all the weight and look at that look
what happens you know it happens right
one trade you hold too long and then you
lose I'm sure you don't hold too long
and then you miss out on a lot of profit
it is what it is it's a lesson you live
and you learn so this trade pulled back
to the area where I wanted to couldn't
get in because it didn't get to the
exact point but prediction was perfectly
on the money the next we have Euro GBP
as you guys can tell I'm sure you guys
around yesterday on Euro GBP I was
explaining how we were waiting for the
breakout of this Zone and once we got
the breakout of the Zone I was then
waiting for a retracement literally
exactly happened four hour eight hours
ago we were up here yesterday and I was
explaining how I was looking for the
pool back to enter the trade line and
look at that exactly what happened and
this is the trade as of right now as you
guys can tell we are currently up about
5 500 on this trade so I was trying to
get in on another entry right here but I
don't have enough margin to be able to
do so but we managed to get into this
entry right here where we pulled back to
the area retested the EMA and now price
is heading to the upset literally
exactly what I said we're gonna retest
this structure retest the EMA and then
head to the upside and that is exactly
what happened so you guys are seeing it
live literally every single tray that I
predicted has pretty much happened to
the T and again another lesson learned
with the trade from yesterday stick to
the plan I could have you know let one
of the positions run and then close the
other one this is like the hard part of
trading this we're 99 of Traders fell
because it's all mindset they don't know
how to control it and this what I teach
the 74 guide students day after day to
do so that being said we'll check in in
the next couple of hours and we'll see
where the trade is all right so there's
a trade up there right now how we're
looking phone one phone two and then
trading the chart everything literally
happening exactly as breaking down I'm
gonna do a Time update so the time the
last time I updated it was 859 I'm gonna
refresh the website now so it's been
about 32 minutes since the last time I
updated uh we're looking good I'm just
gonna keep my eye on the lower time
frames to see if we start having some
slowdown the moment we start having some
slowdown I'm just gonna be smart and
close the profits because I've pretty
much almost tripled the account right
now um because then we're gonna have a
retracement and then I'll be entering
the next trade from here to the upside
because my goal by the end of this week
was to close like around a thousand so I
got to be smart and not be greedy and
like I was explaining now comes the real
skill set which is the mindset because
right now a lot of Traders they want to
close or enter new positions or do
whatever right now I'm just set and
forgetting waiting for the trade to just
uh show me what it's going to do and
then I react and adapt based off of what
it does so stay tuned to the updates
I'll update you guys in the next hour
however long when the market starts
moving around I'm going to stay here for
now with my cat I can't believe I I
would have never thought it happened the
things you do let me make sure you guys
an update what's happening right now
with the drift car they're taking it
once again
you guys can see here back to the shop
so trade updated again for the third
time today in the morning is that just
the Market's moving fast so you got to
react and adapt very fast you can't sit
and forget too long or at least I don't
want to because I'm taking this
challenge very serious and I don't know
how to have any excuses let me show you
how the account is looking right now so
as you guys can see right here let me
just adjust the brightness you guys can
see that the trade is currently pulling
back so I am going to close the trade
right now as you can see last time I
updated it was 931 which is about 20
minutes ago and this is how the trade is
looking right now and I just closed it
on all of the phones let's just open up
all the phones as you can see that is
how much profit we made today as you can
see that was a trade that was closed
today Euro GBP I mean it is heading to
website still but I do believe it's
gonna have this pull back into this
level and I'd rather just be safe than
sorry like we just turned it from 400 to
about a thousand one hundred in under
four hours so I think this is more than
fine I don't want to get greedy and does
have a pullback I'll enter a new trade
here to head to the upside and if not if
this keeps going well I'll just simply
look for another trade so for this trade
we're going to remove this line because
we already predicted this is going to
happen literally perfectly the pullback
and perfectly the push even though I
close exactly where I had the arrow
which I think it gives me goosebumps of
how crazy these positions are all right
so we're back market update coming now I
love that I'm doing this because I'm
realizing how nasty of a Trader I am
like nobody has been able to do what I'm
doing I am calling this precisely like
Candlestick after Candlestick hour after
hour I'm just gonna let my work speak
for itself so as you guys can tell right
here let me show you guys a live market
update so I'm just gonna come up here
what time is it in Miami this is the
last time we refresh the time I'm gonna
go up here refresh the time so it is
about an hour later for not even like 40
minutes and I literally said on why I
wanted to close the market right up here
at this level because I expect affected
a retracement to come back into this
though now that we're at this level now
I'm going to be looking for new entries
to take this trade along but this is
exactly what I am talking about I have
the skill set to be able to catch the
move no one to get out and pretty much
predict every single move I should have
gotten in those cells bro but with that
being said this is a market update as of
right now where the market is
um I'll update you guys in the next
couple of hours if I end up getting into
this trade or not the center forget
strategy that's all I'm gonna say all
right so market update it is eight
o'clock tonight so let me show you guys
how the metatrader is right now so you
guys can see these are all three phones
like usual these are the trades that we
closed earlier on AUD Cad and we all
have obviously the same balance 1173 so
we flipped it from a hundred dollars and
I'm gonna show you guys what I predicted
this morning happened to Perfection but
before that let me show you guys in my
effects book these numbers look crazy
we're up a thousand percent on this
account
um obviously you can see we've taken the
hundred dollars to the Thousand you see
right here we have a total of four
trades that we've taken on the account
obviously we are at a four for four we
haven't lost any trades so far and let
me currently right now so it is
currently 7 47 p.m Miami time and now
I'm going to be showing you guys the
breakdown that I did earlier this
morning how I predicted it and what I'm
looking for next to enter the trade and
on top of that like what I predict is
going to happen tomorrow with a
different pair so let me show you guys
so you guys are you know 7 47 p.m uh
Miami time so this is trading view right
here you guys saw how earlier this
morning I was explaining to you guys on
this time frame how I didn't like how we
had such a strong push and I did
strongly believe we were going to have a
pullback into this level and then in
this level we were looking to go long
well we came back into this level didn't
give me the entry signal that I was
looking for so I stayed away and now we
are currently still in this zone right
here so it is still currently happening
perfectly as I'm anticipating I'm just
waiting for my strategy aligned so I
take the trade so this is where I'm
going to be waiting for a minor break
and then a re-test of this level to then
take the trade to the upside as of right
now this is all that I am looking for on
your GBP which is the trade that got us
to this amount right now in this week so
I'm actually according to plan I'm
already I should already stop trading
this week because I basically flipped
the account two times this week I take
it from about 150 to a thousand this
week alone so I should stop trading into
next week but if any good Trade Centers
present themselves I'm gonna obviously
take it so this is what I'm looking for
your GBP I don't like how this daily
time frame closed because we could have
a pool a deeper pullback like this so
we're going to keep our eye out on that
and the other Market that we were
looking at was GBP Cal you guys saw how
I was explaining this morning how we've
entered a buy here this is our first
trade that took us up fifty dollars and
then we missed this trade and then we're
back at again at this area and I
literally explain to you guys is how I'm
just gonna look to do the same exact
thing I Look to buy here we caught it
and then I look to do it here we didn't
get it look to do it here and now
hopefully I can enter the trade at that
level then another follow-up from this
morning is GBP cat you guys can tell
this is the first trade that we took
under your account I explained I'm
looking to break a book to buy or come
back into here to take the trade long
and then this is where we obviously
missed our entry on this trade it's okay
and then I explained earlier this
morning that if price comes back into
here I'm just going to look to do the
same exact thing again that is literally
by the market again buy it here we
missed it and now I'm going to be
looking for buys here and we kind of
missed it already but it's completely
fine I'm still going to be waiting for
this move right here gonna wait for the
price to break retest and then go to the
upside and then to follow up finally
with AUD CAD which this was the original
trade that we took and closed a little
bit early which we closed around here
this trade has just continued to drop
man this is just insane and the crazy
part is that I called this whole entire
move but I closed it a little bit early
just due to kind of just sticking to the
trading plan and not getting greedy but
this shows you the power of the set and
forget strategy because trend is your
friend and all you have to do is set and
forget so for now we're gonna follow up
with both of those trades your GBP for
Longs tomorrow again and potentially GP
cat so stay tuned to that and actually
let's do one more update Let's do an
update on AUD card I believe AUD card
which is the trade that we already took
uh I'm looking for it to have something
like this a pullback into this area
right here which is going to retest this
support so then we continue taking the
cells to the downside so I'm going to be
waiting for this pullback to then look
for any cells to continue trading with
the trend so I'll catch up with you guys
tomorrow
all right guys so it is 8 45 in the next
morning and once again yesterday's
prediction happened to Perfection let me
show you guys how I got into this trade
and on top of that how I got in a little
bit late because of just the time and
the trade is still effective because of
my strategy because you're trading with
the trend like we are trading live right
now let me actually just show you right
this is the trade that we were breaking
down yesterday that we are currently up
thousand dollars I explained this on
yesterday's trade to Perfection so you
guys can see that yesterday first of all
we're up a thousand dollars on the trade
right now we ended up entering exactly
where I was mentioning it to this line
right here like I'm even getting
Goosebumps as I'm saying this like this
line happened to Perfection look how I
expected this is this is the line from
yesterday this line had the push the
pullback to the zone and look where
Price is Right now exactly where this
line is and I predicted this yesterday
so I'm gonna delete it now because it's
in front of price but yesterday we were
anticipating for price to pull back from
this area here and then this is where I
explained that I didn't get my entry
signal know so I didn't enter the trade
and then all of this obviously we cannot
enter the trade because we are under the
Zone when we broke above the Zone here I
wasn't active in front of the markets
then we dipped under and we broke above
once again this is honestly a little bit
of a late entry I would have loved to
have gotten in around here but obviously
didn't manage to get that I got in at
the break I mean at the closure of this
Candlestick right there on the one hour
which this has got a one hour marabuzu
Candlestick but if you notice it is the
exact same thing that I did here
Candlestick rejection from EMA my area
of Interest Candlestick rejection from
my EMA and then area of interest it's
the same exact thing and I'm predicting
this time and time again I explained to
you guys yesterday I'm going to close
this trade because I am seeing a
pullback here so then continuing going
along close this trade perfectly and
then we waited for the pullback and now
entered another trade so as of right now
this trade is currently it's gonna
refresh the time to show you guys that
it is 847 Miami time so I'm refreshing
it multiple times so you guys see it and
this is where the trade is currently
right now I am going to wait for these
next 12 minutes to then play out because
I can potentially see another push on
this trade to potentially come to this
take profit level as of right now we are
up on this trade not even a one-to-one
risk to reward which is not ideal at all
so this is where I want to ex this is a
little bit glitchy this is what I want a
way for price to come all the way up
there so as of right now predicted the
trade perfectly and then the next trade
that we have in the pipeline is GBP CAD
if you guys remember what I explained
yesterday yesterday on GBP CAD I
explained that I would only look to buy
if we came back into this area here and
would you look at that we're back at
this area again but not only are we at
this area we are rejecting this area
again how we did in the pre previous
times so I don't know if I want to enter
this trade just yet because I like this
one a lot more but in order for me to
enter this trade for a buy just how I
did before just how I predicted here and
just how I predicted here once again in
order for me to enter this trade I have
to close this one because I I don't want
to have too much risk on the table so
I'll update you guys in the next 11
minutes and 25 seconds when this trade
uh when that Candlestick closes because
that would be nine in the morning uh
Miami time so New York session is what
we're trading right now and if it starts
coming back too much I'll probably have
to close because I don't like how this
daily Candlestick is looking as of right
now so I might have to close and just
whatever profits I have just just run
with it
um because it's not gonna lie the entry
was pretty terrible and I can see price
coming back all the way into here to
retest this point and that's way too
close to my entry so I rather just play
it safe and just get whatever profit I
yeah so oh and there's something that I
just realized even if I would have taken
this trade and I just saw this from the
message of the student he literally said
he's like bro anybody could have entered
the trade from the moment you said it
was going to pull back to that area and
everybody would have caught it and I'm
looking at the chart now and it's true
let me show you what I'm talking about
so if I literally would have taken this
trade at this area right here from the
moment that I said it's gonna pull back
so let's say from this point right here
let's say I would have taken it this is
only a 20 pip stop loss this is a super
super super small stop loss so let's say
if somebody did end up taking it here
the average stop loss is usually
anywhere from 15 to 20 Pips for these
small day trades you would have still
been inside this trade so I just
realized that now as I'm checking my
free telegram because I sent it here as
well and in my free telegram I sent it
yesterday at 10 37 in the morning I
literally said hey guys new entry is
loading after I had already predicted
this one in the past I really predicted
it here I said pullback is going to
happen this was on say the day somewhere
up there and then after that the next
day predicted the pullback got out and
then I said new entry loading and now
look at it now everyone should be in
this trade so we still have about four
minutes for this trade to close as you
guys can see right there we're building
that Wick and we are currently up on
this account back up a thousand dollars
I'm
neighbors probably hate me in this car
bro it's probably one of the loudest
cars down there there's some loud ass
cars in this neighborhood I'm gonna be
clear in this
it would be fun they said
[Music]
all right so trade update it's nine in
the morning now the Candlestick
officially closed and let me explain to
you guys my thought process behind this
trade right now you guys can see it is
currently Miami time let me just refresh
this website it is 9 4 in the morning so
the Candlestick that I was expecting to
close right here this is how it closed
this familiar Candlestick closed under
the structure point which I don't like
this at all but I have to I have to take
into consideration this huge four hour
Wick and this right here I say it's a
it's like a 65 to 70 chance it builds it
meaning that this can this next
Candlestick will fill that whole entire
Wick right here but I do have to keep in
mind the daily Candlestick hasn't closed
yet as well if you notice the daily
Candlestick had a huge Wick and then
what did we do the next day we filled it
but we are pulling up now to this
resistance level right here and we've
perfectly rejected from it the four hour
we perfectly rejected from this point
right here as well there's a lot of
things that factor into this trade and
the way that I'm seeing it is the trend
is your friend and I'm just gonna take
it one Candlestick at a time so I'm
gonna wait for this next Candlestick to
close in the next nine minutes because
I've been analyzing this trade for like
five minutes to see what I do
um because truthfully like if this trade
hits my take profit this trade would be
a huge huge huge win for the account and
it kind of needs it in order to keep
this challenge going so if this trade
hits this take profit right here this is
this would be huge
um so I'm just gonna keep monitoring it
one like one Candlestick at a time and
then hopefully if anything if this gives
me a nice entry signal then we'll enter
this trade right here but for now all of
my focus is here
um and yeah I'll just update you guys
each I don't know 30 minutes more or
less I'll do a quick update and then uh
we'll get it we'll get it figured out so
I'll see you guys take it easy all right
so trade out there right now prices put
him back this is where a lot of Traders
fail because all a mindset game and I'm
not going to let my mindset get the best
of me and make me lose this account
again because I know I can achieve this
challenge so this is currently how the
account are looking so price has pulled
back where we were up a thousand
literally a hundred percent of the
account and notice how now price has
pulled back exactly how I had explained
to the area of where I wanted to get out
before but I mean it is what it is
um if you notice price is now having a
pullback but I do strongly believe we
can reject this area right around here
so then we keep heading to the upside so
like I said I'm just going to keep
watching this Candlestick per
Candlestick
um to see if we end up rejecting but as
of right now this is how we are looking
which obviously it hurts but we have to
stick to our strategy and stick to our
parents so I'm going to keep monitoring
this trade and I'm you guys up there all
right so trade up there right now man
this is going a lot more in drawdown
than I expected
um I'm just gonna stick to the plan man
I'm gonna stick to seven forgetting bro
I just gotta do it man like obviously
this hurts seeing the trade up probably
like 2K almost and then now having it
back I'm not gonna say this was a great
thing because I I wasn't in my plan yet
to close so I still had a little bit
more profit in me but I could have
definitely considered getting out of
breaking and if I got a new entry signal
I would have gotten back in but I was up
a thousand dollars now I'm down just
gonna keep watching the trade and I'll
update you guys how it goes so this is
how it's thinking right now where we are
still currently down 500 and this is how
the trade is looking right so I will
update you guys all right so desperate
times call for desperate measure so I'm
here with my boy Sensei and we had to
get him to zoom cough discuss the trade
on what do I do what do I do bro what
was the train not looking good no
and all right I'm just gonna I gotta do
it I'm gonna stick to the plan I gotta
do it sticking to the plan
all right what is up guys so it is
officially Friday 9 31 in the morning
and I'm gonna show you guys not only how
effective the set and forget theory is
but how powerful the set and forget
strategy is and how controlled I am of
my mindset that I have built over the
past five years in the markets because
these type of things happen time and
time and time again so let's get into it
let me explain to you guys what happened
before anything let's show you guys the
trade that I got back in yesterday it's
literally the same exact trade I'll
bring it down right now so we only got
two iPhones right now the Android is
like loading it's doing its thing so
we're basically back inside the same
trade so this is the my effects book you
guys can see it is the same exact
account you guys can see right here the
loss that we had yesterday it was just a
minor breaking loss when price pulled
back to break even
um not a big deal it is what it is it
happens it's the same exact trade and
let me just refresh the time here for
you guys to show you guys that it is 9
30 in the morning so you guys can see
last time I did it was pretty much
yesterday once again I'll refresh it
again 9 32 in the morning so let me
explain to you guys what happened
yesterday so yesterday we took this
trade right here London session had the
push and I explained that I expected the
pullback for New York for then the next
London session to head up obviously this
drawdown right here got to us it was
very deep into the account but I
explained that this area of Interest
right here this support and resistance
very well respected so I anticipated for
price to then reject from here and go
back into profit price went back into
profit but right at that break even line
right there and I decided to close the
trade right at break even because I
didn't want to hold the trade during
Asia's session
um and Tokyo session this is the session
that there is no volume these are the
sessions where there is the most volume
have you noticed this is London session
and then this is New York session right
here London session New York and then
Tokyo and Asia I do not want to be
involved in the market here so I simply
close the trade so what did I do I
Revisited the market again at the same
exact time as I did this time and as I
did this time during London session and
I applied the same exact strategy that I
did here that I did here at this same
exact trade again if you notice I took
the same trade two times but even let's
say if I would have held this trade
right here if I would have never closed
it it would have never hit my stop loss
because this stop loss is perfectly
placed so I didn't have to close it I
just closed it I didn't want to deal
with the emotions of being in this
drawdown right here and then I just
simply entered again and I applied the
same strategy same stop loss same lot
size I even got a better entry than the
first trip so right now we are up on the
account 700 or 600 and we only have
about let me see we're we have about
seven hours left in this daily
Candlestick right now so I strongly do
believe that this whole entire Wick is
going to fill I still do believe and I
actually I even predicted this yesterday
I predicted that this was going to pull
back into this area I predicted that it
was gonna filled in the wick and I even
predicted this once again right guys
I've been
if I can get like a star for how many
things I predicted that would be awesome
so this is another one and I'm just
continuing to apply the strategy and
continuing to do the same exact thing so
for right now I'm just going to wait for
the next Candlestick to close and we're
going to determine if we're going to
hold it or if we're going to close it so
this is for Euro GBP the next trade is
GBP cat as you guys can tell this is the
trade that I was explaining yesterday
that I wanted to go along right here and
we didn't end up doing it because we
were focusing on your GBP and it's the
same trade we've been following with the
same three trades the whole entire week
and look at this now so now it's
breaking which this is very nice because
this is setting up a very nice trade for
next week where we can then have the
retest of this area to then go long and
then last but not least it is AUD CAD so
this is the trade that we had during the
beginning of the week and I explained to
you guys how I was looking for a
pullback to this zone right here to sell
price pulled back to that zone but never
gave me my entry signal so I simply did
not take the trade uh and as of right
now we are having a very steep pullback
which I actually like to see because
that means that this bearish move is
going to continue going next week so we
have a very very interesting next week
but for right now my only focus is
figuring out when am I going to close
this because I do not want to hold this
throughout the weekend so I'll keep you
guys updated on what I end up doing but
this is showing you guys how I'm just
doing the same thing day over day and
just sticking to my plan so yesterday
was very emotional and I'm not gonna say
I'm not an emotional Trader it's just
more of like the emotion of I knew what
I did wrong and I just simply didn't
follow it one thing is just being
emotional because you're emotional and
everything is getting emotional because
you knew you could have avoided the
mistake but you didn't because there was
just pressure on you of thousands of
people watching you so I like that
because if you notice now I'm not going
to let that affect me next week so every
single thing that happens to me within
the week I use it as a lesson for the
next week the first week Lesson Learned
was not so I don't forget too much and
don't be too greedy and have a minimum
of a 2.5 reward what happened this week
I applied that on the first trade cut
the cut the wins a little bit short but
I learned from it and I applied for it
it's not like I ignored it and now this
week is don't let the pressure get to
you so I'm ready to build that up now on
the third week and this is just going to
get better and better and it's going to
take me to complete this challenge so
I'll update you guys in the next hour or
two and we'll see how it goes
there's enough lights
[Music]
I just filled it up we just look at it
look at this guy look at this guy
[Music]
all right so this is final trade update
for the day it is 11 o'clock in the
morning and let me show you guys how the
trade is currently running right now
exactly what I explained to you guys
again has happened so as of right now
you guys can see it is 1103 in the
morning and this is the exact same trade
that we have taken so this is where we
were earlier this morning right here
I'll explain to you guys how I'm Gonna
Keep Holding throughout the day I'm
going to keep holding throughout the
hours let me actually just refresh
things so at 110 in the morning so we
have continued to hold the trade through
the momentum and now we have officially
created a new higher high on the two
hour time frame which is exactly what I
explained this is just going to continue
creating these moves to the upside it's
just going to continue the steps right
now we just happen to be right here up
to this point of the whole entire push
we are currently right now within this
push right here we still have a lot more
room to continue heading to the upside
but the market closes in about five
hours and I don't want to be too greedy
I don't want to be too you know hold the
tray too long I'm pretty much very good
in profit right now more than I needed
for the week and most importantly once
again exactly what I predicted is that
we were going to fill this daily Wick
right here exactly how I experiment
we're going to fill that Wick so as of
right now I'm going to close the trade
where we are for a total gain of sixteen
hundred dollars ending off the week with
a 2700 profit which is very solid and
this is showing you guys the life of a
Trader like the type of decision making
that you have to do like you are one
decision away from cutting the trade
into a little bit of a profit holding it
for a little bit too long taking the
wrong shoe like there you're one slip
decision away from completely changing
your results so that's why it is so
important to have a profitable strategy
to follow so you're in like you never
miss every single time you do it the
correct way so as of right now we're
gonna close the trade where it is right
now and it's been a crazy week but we
are definitely ahead of schedule of what
I originally planned to do so next week
we're looking good to probably about 5k
and most importantly the market is
setting up some very very solid trade
setups for next week some trades that
can probably take this account from the
ending balance all the way up to
probably 10K just next week alone so
make sure you guys tune in to next week
and let's close this trade right now all
right so let's have a recap of how the
week went so we obviously started the
account with 155 which is what we left
off when we left London and obviously
we're back in Miami back in my home in
my office and I'm fully in Focus I have
no distractions and this was a very
interesting week we started off the week
with AUD card how I was anticipating the
rejection from The Head and Shoulders as
well as I was out there drifting where
the drift car ended up breaking down
where I anticipated the retest of the
neckline of the head and shoulders and
then we had a massive move to the
downside as soon as I explained I'm
talking about minutes after everybody on
Instagram telegram Discord everybody
caught this trade because I break it
down live every single day and this is a
beautiful trade because it put me up a
very nice cushion in the account she
gave me a very nice cushion of 450 so I
turned the hundred dollars into 450 in
two trades in just one move because I
say all the time once you predict the
movement of the market it's just
figuring out how you get in on the next
trade and then after that we have your
GPS your GBP gave a check but it played
out in the good sense because obviously
we're trading with the trend we're using
our set and forget strategy so we
entered off the first move I anticipated
the beautiful push off of the area
adventures and then we closed due to the
fact that I anticipated a pullback got
the pullback quickly once the pullback
happened entered again on the trade but
this is where a mistake happened and
that was that I set and forget too long
once again but this time it wasn't I
actually fell asleep and when I woke up
the train had to pull it back because in
my stop loss area but my stop foreign
that we didn't get stopped out price
came back up took us out at break even
and then I entered the same exact trade
with the same exact entry signal during
the next session and that ended up
giving us a nice push where now we have
the account at 2700 So this is a very
very
um interesting week we've gained over 2
000 this week and this is only the
beginning of it I am way ahead of
schedule of what I anticipated to have
for the account and this is due to the
fact that yes I am trading a little bit
more aggressive than I should have but
the market is giving us such great
opportunities that why would I not take
it and most importantly the strategies
align with what the market is getting
and on top of that hundreds if not
thousands of Traders are making money
alongside with this as well so I think
this is going to be a very very
interesting week now coming up for part
three so I would definitely hit that
subscribe button and tune in because I
think we could probably turn next week
into uh probably 10 to 15 000. using the
same exact strategy that's it for
everything for part two of The Challenge
I'll see you guys next week on part
three where I'm going to be taking a
hundred to a million in 60 days that is
the challenge that I'm taking on if you
want to be one of my students if you
want to be someone that follows not only
the trades that I take but trades
alongside with me I want to make
anywhere from a thousand to a thousand
five hundred dollars a week as a
beginner Forex Trader hit the link in
the description below I have a video for
you that's going to show you all the ins
and outs of not only my strategy but of
my community and how you can get better
and you can generate anywhere from a
thousand to a thousand five hundred
dollars a week as a beginner Forex
Trader make sure to hit the link in the
description below hit that like And
subscribe button and I'll see you guys
next week for part three